<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ITALIAN LINK LLC]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ITALIAN LINK LLC]]></description>
        <link>http://www.italianlink.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 16:05:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.italianlink.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1></h1><p>ITALIAN Natural White Limestone for Royal Palace in Kuwait</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e75909424a5d6a9d17d48037234e564c4a0990b0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.539690569429729.1073741833.161750153890441&amp;type=3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ed90f094-d5aa-46f7-af4d-d97b3aa68a7d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BIOCORAL Stone]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BIOCORAL Stone</h1><p>One of our most successful products</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2577c786d4d11a127c90a86fa1287d0a62f5d5d8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/our-biocoral-stone/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4bba7860-f9a1-4026-9914-c16038d42323</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:53:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ZABEEL PALACE - Dubai, UAE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ZABEEL PALACE - Dubai, UAE</h1><p>Royal Palace - Main Gate and West Gate</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/573b4d3e2ea44a2387142086dbca19440d5ea372.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/zabeel-palace-dubai-uae/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">046a906e-c29b-4cd2-91cc-7dbe9f8a05b7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 16:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ABOUT US]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ABOUT US</h1><p>Formed in 2010 under the laws of the U.A.E. in the Emirate of Abu Dhabi, ITALIAN LINK L.L.C. was created and inspired by the passion and experience of Mr Andrea Spadola with the vision of "Linking the World to Quality" Building on unparalleled successes with both private and governmental sectors in Europe and USA, Mr Andrea Spadola was at the forefront of a number of successful projects in the U.A.E. including the supply of stone for the Ministry of Interiors General Administration building in Abu Dhabi, as well as the new Police Stations and the new Civil Defense Buildings in the Abu Dhabi Western Region, Eastern Region and Al Ain. Recognising their niche, Italian Link L.L.C. was established to provide a localised and personal service and to supply premium-quality Italian limestone and other technologically engineered stone products to customers across the MENA region, the GCC and other international markets. Combining the founders twenty years of global experience across consulting, design, manufacture, supply and installation and being backed up by three of Italy’s largest lime stone quarries and stone manufacturers, Italian Link now partners with leading architects and designers to offer a genuinely integrated, fine-quality solution with the scope of deliver personalised support services from the conceptual stages through to the implementation of each project by applying its knowledge and experience to the architectural drawings, pleasing the aesthetic vision as well as being technically ideal for its intended application. With the vision and palette of the Italian designer in mind, the Italian Link L.L.C. team provides value-added consultancy service, helping each customer make informed decisions when selecting the best material for each project and taking into consideration the total cost, to meet the budget. Powered by a team of over 100 professionals and stone specialists, Italian Link L.L.C. uses only premium-quality material, sourced directly from Italy. As every project is unique Italian Link L.L.C. organises and builds the team of specialised master craftsmen at the quarries and factories across Italy, implementing a team of Architects, Engineers and installers that will realise, study and apply the customised specification on a ‘per job’ basis taking into account the characteristics and demands of the desired work to the time frame agreed, superseding the clients expectations and bettering the company’s promises. The Italian Link team as a group provides core competencies such as accounting or finance, business or management experience, industry knowledge, strategic planning experience and customer-based experience or knowledge. The team constructively challenge and help develop proposals on strategy, review the performance of management in meeting agreed goals and objectives, and monitor the reporting of performance. The company also imports marbles, tiles and granites to satisfy the specific needs of each client maintaining its distinct competitive edge in the market as it deals directly with top-tier stone suppliers from Europe, Brazil and other prominent suppliers, eliminating the need of a third party and thereby achieving significant cost savings that are passed on to the clients. Moreover, the company adheres to strict environmental norms and green building specifications to provide a full range of products and services that deliver minimal environmental impact and complement the sustainable development initiatives being implemented across the region. Italian Link’s client portfolio includes high-profile developers and contractors across the region as well as SMEs looking for cost-effective, high-quality limestone</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/italian-link-general-trading-llc-was-formed-by-mr-andrea/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">be47c6ee-362d-4b90-87e3-97421cda9938</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:53:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NURAY ISLAND - Luxury Villas in private island Abu Dhabi, U.A.E.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>NURAY ISLAND - Luxury Villas in private island Abu Dhabi, U.A.E.</h1><p>Supply of Italian Limestone for NURAY ISLAND - Luxury Villas in private island Abu Dhabi, U.A.E.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/607a17158664b3a4802d311bc51f4dc0f638238f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/nuray-island-luxury-villas-in-private-island-abu-dhabi-u/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e194400e-63d6-4fe2-a686-d3b8d868f9b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:45:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ministry of Interior Project - UAE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ministry of Interior Project - UAE</h1><p>ITALIAN LINK supplied successfully 43.681 m2 of Italian BIOCORAL (yellow) & BIANCO ROCCIA (white) cladding for the Ministry of Interior General Administration Building in Abu Dhabi U.A.E.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a58a236d1911a3d5b60195b85d341e68a7010fae.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/ministry-of-interior-project/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">77a7471b-6f89-43e9-a620-f31e4590db59</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:54:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Civil Defense Project - UAE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Civil Defense Project - UAE</h1><p>Supply of BIOCORAL cladding for various CIVIL DEFENSE Stations - Abu Dhabi, Al Ain & Western Region U.A.E.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f533b8e11fd771ca2aef140ea147ef8d38e97778.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/civil-defense-project-uae/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6faf885e-86f9-4110-a996-cae3fb191031</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residential Project - Bahrain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Residential Project - Bahrain</h1><p>CLIENT : SUNNY WAQF DIRECTORATE, GOVERNMENT OF BAHRAIN Supply of 22.000 M2 of BIOCORAL RC56 (yellow) Italian Cladding</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b2c25dd8e807e4ff337889552b97667e4f6ea4ba.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.italianlink.com/residential-project-bahrain/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9eecc3af-2e72-4471-8bdb-78e08c299010</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>