<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ITALIAN LINK LLC - Linking the World to Quality...]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ITALIAN LINK LLC - Linking the World to Quality...]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/italian-link-llc/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:26:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/italian-link-llc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://scontent-mxp1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xaf1/v/t1.0-9/10011186_847051072027009_6575558809137297758_n.png?oh=8caaed429956605cf89b625e986ebcfe&oe=574B3CA1">]]></description>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/ITALIAN.LINK.LLC/photos/pb.161750153890441.-2207520000.1457800634./847051072027009/?type=3&amp;theater</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">345266e0-db3e-4580-b7b0-71ea025713c8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Introduction</h1><p>ITALIAN LINK GENERAL TRADING L.L.C. was formed by Mr
Andrea Spadola in 2010, a database of Governmental and high net worth profile customers has been created and satisfied by performance and high quality services and products delivery in the field of supplying natural and semi-natural stone and marble products produced in Italy and delivered by the Italian Link team to its clients in GCC.The market has shown interest to receive quality products with innovative designs and ITALIAN LINK has been able to manage to supply them with a very competitive price.The success of ITALIAN LINK is the possibility to supply Made in Italy products at a very affordable price. This is the reason why clients have been choosing to do business with Italian Link. The new ITALIAN LINK GENERAL TRADING LLC has the ability to source and secure new and innovative products made in Italy and to supply them to the MENA market.The new ITALIAN LINK GENERAL TRADING LLC will carry on supplying building materials specializing on the stone business where the team is already very successful but also will focus on the supply of new products such as kitchens, furniture, ceramics, but also new technologies for construction of environmentally eco-sustainable housing, and will also will supply consultancy services for Italian companies who want to come to do business in the MENA regions. Moreover a section of Italian food supply will be established due to the family business of Mr Andrea Spadola who holds a network of 150 supermarkets in Italy and the wholesaler network to supply also the customers in UAE.To understand the background and abilities of the team we will give brief description of the existing business performance with the first company ITALIAN LINK Building Materials Trading L.L.C.:Formed in 2010 under the laws of the U.A.E. in the Emirate of Abu Dhabi, Italian Link Building Materials Trading L.L.C. was created and inspired by the passion and experience of Mr Andrea Spadola with passion and the vision of ‘Linking the World to Quality’Building on unparallel successes with both private and governmental sectors in Europe and USA, Mr Andrea Spadola was at the forefront of a number of successful projects in the U.A.E. including the supply of stone for the Ministry of Interiors General Administration building in Abu Dhabi, as well as the new Police Stations and the new Civil Defense Buildings in the Abu Dhabi Western Region, Eastern Region and Al Ain.Recognising their niche, Italian Link Building Materials Trading L.L.C. was established to provide a localised and personal service and to supply premium-quality Italian limestone and other technologically engineered stone products to customers across the MENA region, the GCC and other international markets.Combining the founders twenty years of global experience across consulting, design, manufacture, supply and installation and being backed up by three of Italy’s largest lime stone quarries and stone manufacturers, Italian Link now partners with leading architects and designers to offer a genuinely integrated, fine-quality solution with the scope of deliver personalised support services from the conceptual stages through to the implementation of each project by applying its knowledge and experience to the architectural drawings, pleasing the aesthetic vision as well as being technically ideal for its intended application.With the vision and palette of the Italian designer in mind, the Italian Link L.L.C. team provides value-added consultancy service, helping each customer make informed decisions when selecting the best material for each project and taking into consideration the total cost, to meet the budget.Powered by a team of over 100 professionals and stone specialists, Italian Link L.L.C. uses only premium-quality material, sourced directly from Italy. As every project is unique Italian Link L.L.C. organises and builds the team of specialised master craftsmen at the quarries and factories across Italy, implementing a team of Architects, Engineers and installers that will realise, study and apply the customised specification on a ‘per job’ basis taking into account the characteristics and demands of the desired work to the time frame agreed, superseding the clients expectations and bettering the company’s promises.The Italian Link team as a group provides core competencies such as accounting or finance, business or management experience, industry knowledge, strategic planning experience and customer-based experience or knowledge. The team constructively challenge and help develop proposals on strategy, review the performance of management in meeting agreed goals and objectives, and monitor the reporting of performance.The company also imports marbles, tiles and granites to satisfy the specific needs of each client maintaining its distinct competitive edge in the market as it deals directly with top-tier stone suppliers from Europe, Brazil and other prominent suppliers, eliminating the need of a third party and thereby achieving significant cost savings that are passed on to the clients.Moreover, the company adheres to strict environmental norms and green building specifications to provide a full range of products and services that deliver minimal environmental impact and complement the sustainable development initiatives being implemented across the region.Italian Link’s client portfolio includes high-profile developers and contractors across the region as well as SMEs looking for cost-effective, high-quality limestone</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/italian-link-llc/italian-link-general-trading-llc-was-formed-by-mr-andrea/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">be47c6ee-362d-4b90-87e3-97421cda9938</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 17:54:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/ITALIAN.LINK.LLC/photos/a.575044265894359.1073741835.161750153890441/575044612560991/?type=3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d3c12caa-fce8-45a2-993c-280ac28a4e28</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>ITALIAN LINK L.L.C. - Abu Dhabi - U.A.E. added a new photo.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/ITALIAN.LINK.LLC/photos/a.539610169437769.1073741826.161750153890441/539712909427495/?type=3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">342da4a4-a34b-49c0-8802-464fa4474cd0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Supply of Italian Limestone for NURAY ISLAND - Luxury Villas in private island Abu Dhabi, U.A.E.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/ITALIAN.LINK.LLC/photos/ms.c.eJw1ysENACAIA8CNDBShdv~;FjBKel1yGSpJp41C5sg2w4OA42vVMM8tv3~_P~_znG14wKtIRNf.bps.a.539699839428802.1073741834.161750153890441/539699909428795/?type=3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e26132e2-a7e1-4547-ba82-3f5c0e020b15</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img alt="Supply of BIOCORAL RC56 &lpar;yellow&rpar; for the UROLOGY HOSPITAL in Kuwait City" src="https://scontent.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-frc3/t31.0-0/p180x540/919410_539677322764387_823407179_o.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.539673112764808.1073741832.161750153890441&amp;type=3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dff0cd06-9d42-4eb7-8224-f9fb9f51329c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 17:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>